MORGAN KIGER

Software Developer

O DETAILS O

mkiger95@gmail.com

o SKILLS o

SQL Database

Creative Thinker

Agile Methodologies

Amazon Web Services

Linux/Command Prompt

Efficient Time Management

Requires Minimal Supervision

o LINKS o

www.morgankiger.com

<u>Github</u>

LinkedIn

PROFILE

I am computer engineering student with a minor in math and computer science. I have **3 years of experience** in developing, automation, data reconciliation, SQL databases, and more. Over the years I have led and delivered successful agile-structured projects.

■ EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer at Bonotel Exlcusive Travel

October 2018 - Present

- · Coded automation for data entry process within the business using selenium
- · Coded an automated inventory check that checks availability for all active hotels weekly
- Worked with aws resources like ec2, s3, lambda, and more
- Coded an automated data recon between our booking and billing application
- Built the frontend/backend for an internal tool, where staff could check for rates, download expedia content

IT Intern at Bonotel Exclusive Travel

December 2015 — October 2018

- Mapped hotels to our system, to create a real-time connection for rates
- · Supported all of internal staff with anything tech related

Guest Services/Reservations Agent at Bonotel Exclusive Travel

April 2015 — December 2015

- Handled customer issues in a gracious manner and in accordance with company policies.
- Answered phone calls, liaison between hotel and partner, sold/booked hotel rooms

Shift Manager at Sweet Addiction

August 2012 — May 2014

- Supervised staff and handled all customer service issues
- Handled all money/till at the end of the day, ultimately ran the shop

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, University of Nevada Las Vegas

August 2014 — May 2020

- Minor in Computer Science and Mathematics
- Member of Lambda Chi Alpha
 - Held position: President, Secretary, Alumni Relations

Business Management, West Career & Technical Academy

August 2010 — May 2014

- Advanced Honors Dipolma
- Competed in Future Business Leaders of America's National Competition for two years.
 Received an award for placing 3rd.